<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<head>
   <jokes>
      <record><index>1</index><category>jokes</category><message>An employee applied for leave as follows:"Since I have to go to my village to sell my land along with my wife, please sanction me one-week leave.."</message></record>
      <record><index>2</index><category>jokes</category><message>From an employee who was performing the "mundan" ceremony of his 10 year old son:"as I want to shave my son's head, please leave me for two days.."</message></record>
      <record><index>3</index><category>jokes</category><message>Another gem from CDAC. Leave-letter from an employee who was performing his daughter's wedding: &#8232;"as I am marrying my daughter, please grant a week's leave.."</message></record>
      <record><index>4</index><category>jokes</category><message>&#8232;"As my mother-in-law has expired and I am only one responsible for it, please grant me 10 days leave."</message></record>
      <record><index>5</index><category>jokes</category><message>Another employee applied for half day leave as follows: &#8232;"Since I've to go to the cremation ground at 10 o-clock and I may not return, please grant me half day casual leave"</message></record>
      <record><index>6</index><category>jokes</category><message>An incident of a leave letter:   &#8232;"I am suffering from fever, please declare one-day holiday."</message></record>
      <record><index>7</index><category>jokes</category><message>A leave letter to the headmaster: &#8232;"As I am studying in this school I am suffering from headache. I request you to leave me today"</message></record>
      <record><index>8</index><category>jokes</category><message>Another leave letter written to the headmaster: &#8232;"As my headache is paining, please grant me leave for the day."</message></record>
      <record><index>9</index><category>jokes</category><message>Covering note: &#8232;"I am enclosed herewith..."</message></record>
      <record><index>10</index><category>jokes</category><message>Another one:   &#8232;"Dear Sir: with reference to the above, please refer to my below..."</message></record>
      <record><index>11</index><category>jokes</category><message>Actual letter written for application of leave: &#8232;"My wife is suffering from sickness and as I am her only husband at home I may be granted leave".</message></record>
      <record><index>12</index><category>jokes</category><message>Letter writing:- &#8232;"I am well here and hope you are also in the same well."</message></record>
      <record><index>13</index><category>jokes</category><message>A candidate's job application: &#8232;"This has reference to your advertisement calling for a ' Typist and an Accountant - Male or Female'.... As I am both(!! )for the past several years and I can handle both with good experience, I am applying for the post.</message></record>
      <record><index>14</index><category>jokes</category><message>Crazy Aunt Maud received a letter one morning, and upon reading it burst into floods of tears. “What’s the matter?” asked her companion. “Oh dear,” sobbed Auntie, “It’s my favorite nephew. He’s got three feet.” “Three feet?” exclaimed her friend. “Surely that’s not possible?” “Well,” said Auntie, “his mother’s just written to tell me he’s grown another foot !”</message></record>
      <record><index>15</index><category>jokes</category><message>Are you writing a thank you letter to Grandma like I told you to? Yes Mom. Your handwriting seems very large. Well, Grandma’s very deaf, so I m writing very loudly.</message></record>
      <record><index>16</index><category>jokes</category><message>A student's leave letter:"As I am suffering from my uncle's marriage I cannot attend the class....."</message></record>
      <record><index>17</index><category>jokes</category><message>Husband asks, do you know the meaning of WIFE. It means… Without Information fighting every time! WIFE says No, it means - With Idiot For Ever</message></record>
      <record><index>18</index><category>jokes</category><message>I.T.I., Lahore: An employee applied for leave as follows:Since I have to go to my village to sell my land along with my wife. Please sanction me one-week leave.</message></record>
      <record><index>19</index><category>jokes</category><message>Another employee applied for half day leave as follows:"Since I've to go to the cremation ground at 10 o-clocks and I may not return, please grant me half day casual leave"</message></record>
      <record><index>20</index><category>jokes</category><message>A leave letter to the headmaster:"As I am studying in this school I am suffering from headache. I request you to leave me today"</message></record>
      <record><index>21</index><category>jokes</category><message>Which two letters are rotten for your teeth? D K</message></record>
      <record><index>22</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why is the letter “t” so important to a stick insect? Without it would be a sick insect.</message></record>
      <record><index>23</index><category>jokes</category><message>Have you ever seen a duchess? Yes – it’s the same as an English “s”</message></record>
      <record><index>24</index><category>jokes</category><message>What do snakes write on the bottom of their letters? With love and hisses</message></record>
      <record><index>25</index><category>jokes</category><message>What’s the definition of a school report? A poison pen letter from the principal.</message></record>
      <record><index>26</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why did the young witch have such difficulty writing letters? She had never learned to spell properly.</message></record>
      <record><index>27</index><category>jokes</category><message>What kind of letters did the snake get from his admirers? Fang mail.</message></record>
      <record><index>28</index><category>jokes</category><message>What’s a zombie say when he gets a letter from his girlfriend? It’s a dead letter day.</message></record>
      <record><index>29</index><category>jokes</category><message>How does a ghost start a letter? Tomb it may concern.</message></record>
      <record><index>30</index><category>jokes</category><message>Last night I wrote myself a letter. But I forgot to sign it and now I don’t know who it’s from.</message></record>
      <record><index>31</index><category>jokes</category><message>What did the werewolf write at the bottom of the letter? Best vicious . . </message></record>
      <record><index>32</index><category>jokes</category><message>How did skeletons send each other letters in the days of the Wild West? By Bony Express.</message></record>
      <record><index>33</index><category>jokes</category><message>Teacher: Frd, give me a sentence starting with “I.” Fred: I is . . . Teacher: No, Fred. You must always say “I am.” Fred: Oh, right. I am the ninth letter of the alphabet.</message></record>
      <record><index>34</index><category>jokes</category><message>I got an anonymous letter today. Oh, really – who was it from?!</message></record>
      <record><index>35</index><category>jokes</category><message>1st vampire: How things? 2nd vampire: Terrible! Today I received a letter saying I m overdrawn by 50 pints at the blood bank.</message></record>
      <record><index>36</index><category>jokes</category><message>What word allows you to take away two letters and get one? Stone.</message></record>
      <record><index>37</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why did the witch’s mail rattle? A: It was a chain letter.</message></record>
      <record><index>38</index><category>jokes</category><message>What does an envelope say when you lick it? Nothing. It just shuts up.</message></record>
      <record><index>39</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why do postmen carry letters? Because the letters can’t go anywhere by themselves.</message></record>
      <record><index>40</index><category>jokes</category><message>What letter is like a vegetable? The letter P.</message></record>
      <record><index>41</index><category>jokes</category><message>Where do you put letters to boys? In a mail (male) box.</message></record>
      <record><index>42</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why is the letter N the most powerful letter? Because it is in the middle of TNT.</message></record>
      <record><index>43</index><category>jokes</category><message>How many letters are there in the alphabet? Eleven. T-H-E A-L-P-H-A-B-E-T.</message></record>
      <record><index>44</index><category>jokes</category><message>Which two letters of the alphabet are nothing? MT (empty) .</message></record>
      <record><index>45</index><category>jokes</category><message>What letter should you avoid? The letter A because it makes men mean.</message></record>
      <record><index>46</index><category>jokes</category><message>What 8-letter word has one letter in it? Envelope.</message></record>
      <record><index>47</index><category>jokes</category><message>What letter stands for the ocean? The letter C.</message></record>
      <record><index>48</index><category>jokes</category><message>What two words have thousands of letters in them? Post office.</message></record>
      <record><index>49</index><category>jokes</category><message>What did the envelope say to the stamp? “Stick with me and we ll go places.”</message></record>
      <record><index>50</index><category>jokes</category><message>What did the stamp say to the envelope? “I’ve become attached to you.”</message></record>
      <record><index>51</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why did the boy jump up and down on the letter? He heard that you have to stamp letters or the post office won’t send them.</message></record>
      <record><index>52</index><category>jokes</category><message>Why do people leave letters at the football ground ? They want to catch the last goal-post !</message></record>
      <record><index>53</index><category>jokes</category><message>What do you call a Welshman who writes lots of letters ? Pen Gwyn !</message></record>
      <record><index>54</index><category>jokes</category><message>His girlfriend returned all his letters. I bet she marked them “second class male !”</message></record>
      <record><index>55</index><category>jokes</category><message>What letters are not in the alphabet? The ones in the mail, of course!</message></record>
      <record><index>56</index><category>jokes</category><message>What two letters do you say when you answer the phone? LO</message></record>
      <record><index>57</index><category>jokes</category><message>TYPEWRITER is the longest word that can be made using the letters only on one row of the keyboard.</message></record>
      <record><index>58</index><category>jokes</category><message>"Go." is the shortest complete sentence in the English language.</message></record>
      <record><index>59</index><category>jokes</category><message>The sentence "the quick brown fox jumps over the lazy dog" uses every letter in the English language.</message></record>
      <record><index>60</index><category>jokes</category><message>China has more English speakers than the United States. </message></record>
      <record><index>61</index><category>jokes</category><message>"Rhythms" is the longest English word without vowels.</message></record>
      <record><index>62</index><category>jokes</category><message>"Queueing" is the only word with five consecutive vowels.</message></record>
      <record><index>63</index><category>jokes</category><message>"Q" is the only letter that is not used in the name of any of the United States.</message></record>
      <record><index>64</index><category>jokes</category><message>The letters H, I, O, and X are the only letters that look the same if you flip them upside down or view them from behind.</message></record>
      <record><index>65</index><category>jokes</category><message>Most commonly used word in English? THE. The second and the third place go to OF and AND respectively.</message></record>
      <record><index>66</index><category>jokes</category><message>The longest word that does not need both E and T is PhilosophicoPsychologically (27-letters).</message></record>
      <record><index>67</index><category>jokes</category><message>Canada is an indian word meaning "Big Village".</message></record>
      <record><index>68</index><category>jokes</category><message>Facetious and abstemious contain all the vowels in the correct order, as does arsenious, meaning "containing arsenic."</message></record>
      <record><index>69</index><category>jokes</category><message>Only two English words in current use end in "-gry". They are "angry" and "hungry".</message></record>
      <record><index>70</index><category>jokes</category><message>More English words begin with the letter "s" than with any other letter.</message></record>
      <record><index>71</index><category>jokes</category><message>If Olive Oil is made from Olives and Vegetable oils from Vegetables, then what is Baby oil made from???</message></record>
      <record><index>72</index><category>jokes</category><message>Photographer: My secret of success is? 'Think negative'!</message></record>
      <record><index>73</index><category>jokes</category><message>Those 8 seconds really become so longer when you wait for "Skip" option button on video sharing site!</message></record>
      <record><index>74</index><category>jokes</category><message>World's shortest Joke ever is when Doctor asks: How's your headache? 
Patient: She is fine!</message></record>
      <record><index>75</index><category>jokes</category><message>I always learn from the mistake of others who take my advice.</message></record>
      <record><index>76</index><category>jokes</category><message>I love watching scary movies!" *10 minutes later* "Friend walk me to the bathroom.</message></record>
      <record><index>77</index><category>jokes</category><message>f a man smiles all the time, he’s probably selling something that doesn’t work.</message></record>
      <record><index>78</index><category>jokes</category><message>I am sure that I am an awesome singer but when no one is listening.</message></record>
      <record><index>79</index><category>jokes</category><message>I don’t even know how to spell anymore. I type the 1st half of the word and wait for auto correct to do the rest.!!</message></record>
      <record><index>80</index><category>jokes</category><message>I’m not judgmental, so when I see a person driving slow in the fast lane, I never assume what gender she is…</message></record>
      <record><index>81</index><category>jokes</category><message>Law of cigarette smoking:
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
.
Smoke always goes
in the direction of non-smokers .</message></record>
      <record><index>82</index><category>jokes</category><message>Dear girls…
If you love him, let him go. If he returns, he’s Batman.
Because batman returns…</message></record>
      <record><index>83</index><category>jokes</category><message>Dear girls…
If you love him, let him go. If he returns, he’s Batman.
Because batman returns…</message></record>
      <record><index>84</index><category>jokes</category><message>They tie dog to the pole..
So they don’t move.
That’s how I feel
When someone sitting with cellphone attached to a charger…</message></record>
      <record><index>85</index><category>jokes</category><message>Did you hear about the blind carpenter who picked up his hammer and saw? Did you hear about the deaf shepherd who gathered his flock and heard (herd)? 

If you don't understand these, use your dictionary and look up the words "blind," "deaf," "saw," "heard" and "herd." </message></record>
      <record><index>86</index><category>jokes</category><message>A teacher is talking to a student.
Teacher: Did your father help you with your homework? 
Student: No, he did it all by himself.</message></record>
      <record><index>87</index><category>jokes</category><message>On a crowded bus, one man noticed that another man had his eyes closed. 
"What's the matter? Are you sick?" 
"No, I'm okay. It's just that I hate to see an old lady standing." </message></record>
      <record><index>88</index><category>jokes</category><message>A man was complaining to a railroad engineer. 

What's the use of having a train schedule if the trains are always late. 

The railroad engineer replied. 

How would we know they were late, if we didn't have a schedule?</message></record>
      <record><index>89</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: "I was born in California." 
B: "Which part?" 
A: "All of me."</message></record>
      <record><index>90</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: "Excuse me. Do you know the way to the zoo?" 
B: "No, I'm sorry I don't." 
A: "Well, it's two blocks this way, then one block to the left." </message></record>
      <record><index>91</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What has many keys but can't open any doors? 
A: A piano.</message></record>
      <record><index>92</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: Can a kangaroo jump higher than the Empire State Building? 
A: Yes, because the Empire State Building can't jump! </message></record>
      <record><index>93</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What letter of the alphabet is an insect?
A: B. (bee)</message></record>
      <record><index>94</index><category>jokes</category><message>In the classroom the teacher is asking a student to do something. 

Teacher: Tell me a sentence that starts with "I." 

Student: I is the ... 

Teacher: Stop! Never put "is" after "I." Always put 'am' after "I." 

Student: OK. I am the ninth letter of the alphabet. </message></record>
      <record><index>95</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: John says I'm pretty. Andy says I'm ugly. What do you think, Peter? 

B: I think you are pretty ugly. 

Insulting someone is often considered funny, especially when that person is fishing for a complement. 

NOTE: pretty ugly = very ugly </message></record>
      <record><index>96</index><category>jokes</category><message>An elementary school teacher sends this note to all parents on the first day of school. 

"If you promise not to believe everything your child says happens at school, I will promise not to believe everything your child says happens at home. </message></record>
      <record><index>97</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What letter is a body of water?
A: C. (sea) </message></record>
      <record><index>98</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: Doctor, will I be able to play the piano after the operation. 

B: Yes, of course. 

A: Great. I never could before.</message></record>
      <record><index>99</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What starts with E, ends with E and only has one letter? 
A: An envelope.</message></record>
      <record><index>100</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: If you drop a white hat into the Red Sea, what does it become? 
A: Wet.</message></record>
      <record><index>101</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What letter is a drink?
A: T. (tea)</message></record>
      <record><index>102</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What does a ghost eat for dessert?
A: I scream. (Ice cream)</message></record>
      <record><index>103</index><category>jokes</category><message>The teacher says: Today, we're going to talk about the tenses. Now, if I say "I am beautiful," which tense is it?

The student says: Obviously it's the past tense.</message></record>
      <record><index>104</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What do you say to a ghost with three heads?
A: Hello, hello, hello.</message></record>
      <record><index>105</index><category>jokes</category><message>Two factory workers are talking.
The woman says, "I can make the boss give me the day off."
The man replies, "And how would you do that?"
The woman says, "Just wait and see." She then hangs upside-down from the ceiling.
The boss comes in and says, "What are you doing?"
The woman replies, "I'm a light bulb."
The boss then says, "You've been working so much that you've gone crazy. I think you need to take the day off."
The man starts to follow her and the boss says, "Where are you going?"
The man says, "I'm going home, too. I can't work in the dark."</message></record>
      <record><index>106</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What is white when it's dirty and black when it's clean? 
A: A blackboard.</message></record>
      <record><index>107</index><category>jokes</category><message>Two children are talking.

A: Meet my new born brother.
B: Oh, he is so handsome! What's his name?
A: I don't know. I can't understand a word he says.</message></record>
      <record><index>108</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: Where does a ghost mail his letters?
A: At the ghost office. (Post office)</message></record>
      <record><index>109</index><category>jokes</category><message>A guy says to his friend, "Guess how many coins I have in my pocket."

The friend says, "If I guess right, will you give me one of them?"

The first guy says, "If you guess right, I'll give you both of them."</message></record>
      <record><index>110</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What do you call a boomerang that won't come back? 
A: A stick.</message></record>
      <record><index>111</index><category>jokes</category><message>The patient says, "Doctor, you've got to help me. Nobody ever listens to me. No one ever pays any attention to what I have to say.
The doctor says, "Next, please."</message></record>
      <record><index>112</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: Just look at that young person with the short hair and blue jeans. Is it a boy or a girl?
B: It's a girl. She's my daughter.
A: Oh, I'm sorry, sir. I didn't know that you were her father.
B: I'm not. I'm her mother.</message></record>
      <record><index>113</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: Hey, man! Please call me a taxi.
B: Yes, sir. You are a taxi.</message></record>
      <record><index>114</index><category>jokes</category><message>The mother says to her daughter, "Did you enjoy your first at school?"
The daughter answers, "First day? Do you mean I have to go back again tomorrow?"
</message></record>
      <record><index>115</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: Why are you late?
B: There was a man who lost a hundred dollar bill.
A: That's nice. Were you helping him look for it?
B: No, I was standing on it.</message></record>
      <record><index>116</index><category>jokes</category><message>My friend said he knew a man with a wooden leg named Smith.
So I asked him, "What was the name of his other leg?"</message></record>
      <record><index>117</index><category>jokes</category><message>Teacher: What's the past participle of the verb "to ring?"
Student: What do you think, sir?
Teacher: I don't think. I KNOW.
Student: I don't think I know either, sir.</message></record>
      <record><index>118</index><category>jokes</category><message>A man goes to the doctor and says, "Doctor, wherever I touch, it hurts."
The doctor asks, "What do you mean?"
The man says, "When I touch my shoulder, it really hurts.When I touch my knee - OUCH! When I touch my forehead, it really, really hurts."
The doctor says, "I know what's wrong with you. You've broken your finger!" </message></record>
      <record><index>119</index><category>jokes</category><message>A man inserted an ad in the classifieds: "Wife wanted."
The next day he received a hundred letters. They all said the same thing: "You can have mine."</message></record>
      <record><index>120</index><category>jokes</category><message>Principal: "I've had complaints about you, Johnny, from all of your teachers. What have you been doing?"
Johnny: "Nothing, sir."
Principal: "Exactly!"</message></record>
      <record><index>121</index><category>jokes</category><message>A girl and a boy are talking.

The girl says, "You would be a good dancer except for two things."
The boy asks, "What are those two things?"
The girl answers, "Your feet."</message></record>
      <record><index>122</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What are two things people never eat before breakfast?
A: Lunch and supper.
</message></record>
      <record><index>123</index><category>jokes</category><message>The doctor to the patient: "You are very sick."
The patient to the doctor: "Can I get a second opinion?"
The doctor again: "Yes, you are very ugly too."</message></record>
      <record><index>124</index><category>jokes</category><message>A man receives a phone call from his doctor.
The doctor says, "I have some good news and some bad news."
The man says, "OK, give me the good news first."
The doctor says, "The good news is, you have 24 hours to live."
The man replies, "Oh no! If that's the good news, then what's the bad news?"
The doctor says, "The bad news is, I forgot to call you yesterday."</message></record>
      <record><index>125</index><category>jokes</category><message>Two boys were arguing when the teacher entered the room.
The teacher says, "Why are you arguing?"

One boy answers, "We found a ten dollor bill and decided to give it to whoever tells the biggest lie."

"You should be ashamed of yourselves," said the teacher, "When I was your age I didn't even know what a lie was."

The boys gave the ten dollars to the teacher.</message></record>
      <record><index>126</index><category>jokes</category><message>The patient says, "Doctor, I have a pain in my eye whenever I drink tea."
The doctor says, "Take the spoon out of the mug before you drink."</message></record>
      <record><index>127</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What are the 3 important rings in life?
A: Engagement ring, wedding ring, and suffering.</message></record>
      <record><index>128</index><category>jokes</category><message>A: I have the perfect son.
B: Does he smoke?
A: No, he doesn't.
B: Does he drink whiskey?
A: No, he doesn't.
B: Does he ever come home late?
A: No, he doesn't.
B: I guess you really do have the perfect son. How old is he?
A: He will be six months old next Wednesday.</message></record>
      <record><index>129</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: Why are men with pierced ears better suited for marriage?
A: Because they have suffered and bought jewelry.</message></record>
      <record><index>130</index><category>jokes</category><message>Teacher : Correct the sentence,
"A bull and a cow is grazing in the field"

Student : "A cow and a bull is grazing in the field"
Teacher : How?

Student : Ladies first.</message></record>
      <record><index>131</index><category>jokes</category><message>U are a BITCH

Beautiful
Intelligent
Talented
Cute
Hilarious

r u smiling now?
?
?
?
*YOU ARE REALLY BITCH*</message></record>
      <record><index>132</index><category>jokes</category><message>A student is talking to his teacher.

Student: "Would you punish me for something I didn`t do?"
Teacher:" Of course not."
Student: "Good, because I haven't done my homework."</message></record>
      <record><index>133</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: What do tigers have that no other animals have?
A: Baby tigers.</message></record>
      <record><index>134</index><category>jokes</category><message>Wats d height of hope??
It is: sittin in d exam hall,
holdin d question paper in hand
n tellin ur self
“dude,dnt worry.
Exams wil get postponed!”</message></record>
      <record><index>135</index><category>jokes</category><message>A man walks into a shop and sees a cute little dog.
He asks the shopkeeper, "Does your dog bite?"
The shopkeeper says, "No, my dog does not bite."
The man tries to pet the dog and the dog bites him.
"Ouch," he says, "I thought you said your dog does not bite!"
The shopkeeper replies, "That is not my dog."</message></record>
      <record><index>136</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: Why is the number six afraid?
A: Because seven eight nine (seven ate nine)</message></record>
      <record><index>137</index><category>jokes</category><message>A teenage girl had been talking on the phone for about half an hour, and then she hung up.

"Wow!," said her father, "That was short. You usually talk for two hours. What happened?"

"Wrong number," replied the girl.</message></record>
      <record><index>138</index><category>jokes</category><message>Hey U Know
Which is the best day to propose a girl.. April 1
U Know Why??
If she accept its your luck
otherwise just tell April Foooooll.</message></record>
      <record><index>139</index><category>jokes</category><message>Man : How old is your father?
Boy : As old as me.
Man : How can that be?
Boy : He became a father only when I was born</message></record>
      <record><index>140</index><category>jokes</category><message>Love is one long sweet dream, and marriage is the alarm clock. </message></record>
      <record><index>141</index><category>jokes</category><message>Q: How many legs does an ant have?
A: Two, the same as an uncle.
(HINT: ant = aunt)</message></record>
      <record><index>142</index><category>jokes</category><message>Rain of summer, snow of winter,
grace of autumn, glory of spring,
May beauty of every season
give ur heart a beautiful reason 2 smile.
May God suceed u in every exams of ur life.
Good luck &amp; all the best</message></record>
      <record><index>143</index><category>jokes</category><message>Good FRIENDS are hard to find,
harder to leave,
and impossible to forget.</message></record>
      <record><index>144</index><category>jokes</category><message>eXams are there,
at the paper u stare;
the answer is nowhere,
which makes u pull ur hair.
The teachers make u glare,
the grades r not fair,
but just like the past 20 yrs,
WE DONT CARE !!</message></record>
      <record><index>145</index><category>jokes</category><message>eXams are there,
at the paper u stare;
the answer is nowhere,
which makes u pull ur hair.
The teachers make u glare,
the grades r not fair,
but just like the past 20 yrs,
WE DONT CARE !!</message></record>
      <record><index>146</index><category>jokes</category><message>To be a “Good professional”,
always start to study late for “Exams”.
Because it teaches how to manage “Time”
and tackle “Emergencies”!!</message></record>
      <record><index>147</index><category>jokes</category><message>Exams are like Girl friends
- Too many questions
- Difficult to understand
- More explanation is needed
- Result is always fail!</message></record>
      <record><index>148</index><category>jokes</category><message>A student grabbed a coin,

Flipped it in the air &amp; said,
“Head, I go to sleep.”

Tail, I watch a movie.

If it stands on the edge I’ll study</message></record>
      <record><index>149</index><category>jokes</category><message>It takes 15 trees to
produce the amount
of paper that we
use to write one exam.

join us in promoting the noble
cause of saving trees.
SAY NO TO EXAMS</message></record>
      <record><index>150</index><category>jokes</category><message>Child Donkey: Mum with whom shall I play, every donkey is busy. Mother Donkey: Don't worry son, see here, this donkey will be free after reading this joke.</message></record>
   </jokes>
   <twisters>
      <record><index>1001</index><category>twisters</category><message>"A big black bug bit a big black dog on his big black nose."</message></record>
      <record><index>1002</index><category>twisters</category><message>"A tricky frisky snake with sixty super scaly stripes."</message></record>
      <record><index>1003</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Eleven owls licked eleven little liquorice lollipops."</message></record>
      <record><index>1004</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Fresh fried fish, fish fresh fried, fried fish fresh, fish fried fresh."</message></record>
      <record><index>1005</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Friendly fleas and fireflies."</message></record>
      <record><index>1006</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Fuzzy wuzzy was a bear. Fuzzy wuzzy had no hair. Fuzzy wuzzy wasn't very fuzzy, was he?"</message></record>
      <record><index>1007</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Give papa a cup of proper coffee in a copper coffee cup." </message></record>
      <record><index>1008</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Greek grapes, Greek grapes, Greek grapes..."</message></record>
      <record><index>1009</index><category>twisters</category><message>"How much wood would a woodchuck chuck if a woodchuck could chuck wood"</message></record>
      <record><index>1010</index><category>twisters</category><message>"I scream you scream we all scream for ice cream..."</message></record>
      <record><index>1011</index><category>twisters</category><message>"If two witches were watching two watches, which witch would watch which watch?"</message></record>
      <record><index>1012</index><category>twisters</category><message>"If you want to buy, buy, if you don't want to buy, bye bye!"</message></record>
      <record><index>1013</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Kitty caught the kitten in the kitchen."</message></record>
      <record><index>1014</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Not these things here, but those things there." </message></record>
      <record><index>1015</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Quick kiss, quick kiss, quick kiss."</message></record>
      <record><index>1016</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Red leather yellow leather."</message></record>
      <record><index>1017</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Red lorry, yellow lorry." </message></record>
      <record><index>1018</index><category>twisters</category><message>"She sells sea shells by the sea shore."</message></record>
      <record><index>1019</index><category>twisters</category><message>"The big bug bit the little beetle, but the little beetle bit the big bug back." </message></record>
      <record><index>1020</index><category>twisters</category><message>"The blue bluebird blinks."</message></record>
      <record><index>1021</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Three free throws."</message></record>
      <record><index>1022</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Toy phone, Toy phone, Toy phone..."</message></record>
      <record><index>1023</index><category>twisters</category><message>"Zebras zig and zebras zag."</message></record>
      <record><index>1024</index><category>twisters</category><message>“A big black bug bit a big black dog on his big black nose!”</message></record>
      <record><index>1025</index><category>twisters</category><message>“A fat thrush flies through thick fog.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1026</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Birdie birdie in the sky laid a turdie in my eye.&#8232;If cows could fly I'd have a cow pie in my eye.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1027</index><category>twisters</category><message>“black back bat”</message></record>
      <record><index>1028</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Black background, brown background.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1029</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Can you can a can as a canner can can a can?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1030</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Casual clothes are provisional for leisurely trips across Asia.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1031</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Clean clams crammed in clean cans.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1032</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Coy knows pseudonoise codes.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1033</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Denise sees the fleece,&#8232;Denise sees the fleas.&#8232;At least Denise could sneeze&#8232;and feed and freeze the fleas.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1034</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Did Dick Pickens prick his pinkie pickling cheap cling peaches in an inch of Pinch or framing his famed French finch photos?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1035</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Double bubble gum, bubbles double.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1036</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Elizabeth's birthday is on the third Thursday of this month.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1037</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Excited executioner exercising his excising powers excessively.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1038</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Four furious friends fought for the phone.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1039</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Green glass globes glow greenly.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1040</index><category>twisters</category><message>“He threw three balls.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1041</index><category>twisters</category><message>“How can a clam cram in a clean cream can?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1042</index><category>twisters</category><message>“How many berries could a bare berry carry,&#8232;if a bare berry could carry berries?&#8232;Well they can't carry berries”</message></record>
      <record><index>1043</index><category>twisters</category><message>“How many boards&#8232;Could the Mongols hoard&#8232;If the Mongol hordes got bored?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1044</index><category>twisters</category><message>“How many cookies could a good cook cook If a good cook could cook cookies? A good cook could cook as much cookies as a good cook who could cook cookies.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1045</index><category>twisters</category><message>“How much ground would a groundhog hog, if a groundhog could hog ground? A groundhog would hog all the ground he could hog, if a groundhog could hog ground.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1046</index><category>twisters</category><message>“How much pot, could a pot roast roast, if a pot roast could roast pot.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1047</index><category>twisters</category><message>“I eat eel while you peel eel”</message></record>
      <record><index>1048</index><category>twisters</category><message>“I saw Susie sitting in a shoe shine shop.&#8232;Where she sits she shines, and where she shines she sits.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1049</index><category>twisters</category><message>“I stood sadly on the silver steps of Burgess's fish sauce shop, mimicking him hiccuping, and wildly welcoming him within.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1050</index><category>twisters</category><message>“I thought, I thought of thinking of thanking you.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1051</index><category>twisters</category><message>“I wish to wash my Irish wristwatch.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1052</index><category>twisters</category><message>“I wish to wish the wish you wish to wish, but if you wish the wish the witch wishes, I won't wish the wish you wish to wish.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1053</index><category>twisters</category><message>“If Pickford's packers packed a packet of crisps would the packet of crisps that Pickford's packers packed survive for two and a half years?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1054</index><category>twisters</category><message>“If Stu chews shoes, should Stu choose the shoes he chews?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1055</index><category>twisters</category><message>“If you're keen on stunning kites and cunning stunts,&#8232;buy a cunning stunning stunt kite.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1056</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Near an ear, a nearer ear, a nearly eerie ear.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1057</index><category>twisters</category><message>“One-one was a race horse.&#8232;Two-two was one too.&#8232;One-one won one race.&#8232;Two-two won one too.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1058</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers.&#8232;A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked.&#8232;If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers,&#8232;Where's the peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1059</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Picky people pick Peter Pan Peanut-Butter, 'tis the peanut-butter picky people pick.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1060</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Pirates Private Property”</message></record>
      <record><index>1061</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Rhys watched Ross switch his Irish wristwatch for a Swiss wristwatch.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1062</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Roberta ran rings around the Roman ruins.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1063</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Rolling red wagons”</message></record>
      <record><index>1064</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Roofs of mushrooms rarely mush too much.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1065</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Sam's shop stocks short spotted socks.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1066</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Santa's Short Suit Shrunk”</message></record>
      <record><index>1067</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Send toast to ten tense stout saints' ten tall tents.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1068</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Seth at Sainsbury's sells thick socks.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1069</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Seven slick slimey snakes slowly sliding southward.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1070</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Seventy seven benevolent elephants”</message></record>
      <record><index>1071</index><category>twisters</category><message>“She saw Sherif's shoes on the sofa. But was she so sure she saw Sherif's shoes on the sofa?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1072</index><category>twisters</category><message>“She stood on the balcony inexplicably mimicking him hiccuping, and amicably welcoming him home.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1073</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Sheena leads, Sheila needs.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1074</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Singing Sammy sung songs on sinking sand.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1075</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Six sharp smart sharks.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1076</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Six sick hicks nick six slick bricks with picks and sticks.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1077</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Six sleek swans swam swiftly southwards”</message></record>
      <record><index>1078</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Sounding by sound is a sound method of sounding sounds.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1079</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Stupid superstition!”</message></record>
      <record><index>1080</index><category>twisters</category><message>“The great Greek grape growers grow great Greek grapes.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1081</index><category>twisters</category><message>“The owner of the inside inn was inside his inside inn with his inside outside his inside inn.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1082</index><category>twisters</category><message>“The queen in green screamed.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1083</index><category>twisters</category><message>“The thirty-three thieves thought that they thrilled the throne throughout Thursday.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1084</index><category>twisters</category><message>“There those thousand thinkers were thinking how did the other three thieves go through.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1085</index><category>twisters</category><message>“There was a fisherman named Fisher&#8232;who fished for some fish in a fissure.&#8232;Till a fish with a grin,&#8232;pulled the fisherman in.&#8232;Now they're fishing the fissure for Fisher.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1086</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Thin grippy thick slippery.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1087</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Thirty-three thirsty, thundering thoroughbreds thumped Mr. Thurber on Thursday.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1088</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Three short sword sheaths.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1089</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Tie twine to three tree twigs.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1090</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Two tried and true tridents”</message></record>
      <record><index>1091</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Unique New York.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1092</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Wayne went to Wales to watch walruses.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1093</index><category>twisters</category><message>“We surely shall see the sun shine soon.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1094</index><category>twisters</category><message>“We're real rear wheels.”</message></record>
      <record><index>1095</index><category>twisters</category><message>“what a terrible tongue twister,&#8232;what a terrible tongue twister...”</message></record>
      <record><index>1096</index><category>twisters</category><message>“What time does the wristwatch strap shop shut?”</message></record>
      <record><index>1097</index><category>twisters</category><message>“When you write copy you have the right to copyright the copy you write. ...”</message></record>
      <record><index>1098</index><category>twisters</category><message>“You cuss, I cuss, we all cuss, for asparagus!”</message></record>
      <record><index>1099</index><category>twisters</category><message>“Zero zebras zig zagged into the zoo."</message></record>
      <record><index>1100</index><category>twisters</category><message>If you must cross a course cross cow across a crowded cow crossing, cross the cross coarse cow across the crowded cow crossing carefully. </message></record>
   </twisters>
   <facts>
      <record><index>2001</index><category>facts</category><message>“When I die, I want to die like my grandfather who died peacefully in his sleep. Not screaming like all the passengers in his car.” - Will Rogers</message></record>
      <record><index>2002</index><category>facts</category><message>“A citizen of America will cross the ocean to fight for democracy, but won’t cross the street to vote in a national election.” - Bill Vaughan</message></record>
      <record><index>2003</index><category>facts</category><message>“A friend is someone who will bail you out of jail. A best friend is the one sitting next to you saying ‘boy was that fun.’”</message></record>
      <record><index>2004</index><category>facts</category><message>“At every party there are two kinds of people: those who want to go home and those who don’t. The trouble is, they are usually married to each other.” - Ann Landers</message></record>
      <record><index>2005</index><category>facts</category><message>“By the time a man realizes that his father was right, he has a son who thinks he’s wrong.” - Charles Wadsworth</message></record>
      <record><index>2006</index><category>facts</category><message>“Having sex is like playing bridge. If you don’t have a good partner, you’d better have a good hand.” - Woody Allen</message></record>
      <record><index>2007</index><category>facts</category><message>“How is it one careless match can start a forest fire, but it takes a whole box to start a campfire?” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2008</index><category>facts</category><message>“I am going to call my kids Ctrl, Alt and Delete. Then if they muck up I will just hit them all at once.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2009</index><category>facts</category><message>“I dream of a better tomorrow, where chickens can cross the road and not be questioned about their motives.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2010</index><category>facts</category><message> “I have enough money to last me the rest of my life, unless I buy something.” - Jackie Mason</message></record>
      <record><index>2011</index><category>facts</category><message>“I have to exercise early in the morning before my brain figures out what I’m doing.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2012</index><category>facts</category><message>“I’m at the age where I want two girls. In case I fall asleep they will have someone to talk to.” - Rodney Dangerfield</message></record>
      <record><index>2013</index><category>facts</category><message>“If evolution is fact, why do mothers only have two hands?” - Milton Berle</message></record>
      <record><index>2014</index><category>facts</category><message>“Knowledge is knowing a tomato is a fruit; Wisdom is not putting it in a fruit salad.” - Brian Gerald O’Driscoll</message></record>
      <record><index>2015</index><category>facts</category><message>“To err is human, to blame it on somebody else shows management potential.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2016</index><category>facts</category><message>“A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don’t need it.” - Bob Hope</message></record>
      <record><index>2017</index><category>facts</category><message>“A bargain is something you don’t need at a price you can’t resist.” - Franklin Jones</message></record>
      <record><index>2018</index><category>facts</category><message>“A celebrity is someone who works hard all his life to become known and then wears dark glasses to avoid being recognized.” - Fred Allen</message></record>
      <record><index>2019</index><category>facts</category><message>“A computer once beat me at chess, but it was no match for me at kick boxing.” - Emo Philips</message></record>
      <record><index>2020</index><category>facts</category><message>“A graduation ceremony is an event where the commencement speaker tells thousands of students dressed in identical caps and gowns that ‘individuality’ is the key to success.” - Robert Purvis</message></record>
      <record><index>2021</index><category>facts</category><message>“A stockbroker urged me to buy a stock that would triple its value every year. I told him, ‘At my age, I don’t even buy green bananas.’” - Claude Pepper</message></record>
      <record><index>2022</index><category>facts</category><message>“Always borrow money from a pessimist. He won’t expect it back.” - Oscar Wilde</message></record>
      <record><index>2023</index><category>facts</category><message>“America is a country where half the money is spent buying food, and the other half is spent trying to lose weight.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2024</index><category>facts</category><message>“As you get older three things happen. The first is your memory goes, and I can’t remember the other two.” - Norman Wisdom</message></record>
      <record><index>2025</index><category>facts</category><message>“Before you criticize someone, you should walk a mile in their shoes. That way when you criticize them, you are a mile away from them and you have their shoes.” - Jack Handey</message></record>
      <record><index>2026</index><category>facts</category><message>“Better to remain silent and be thought a fool, than to speak and remove all doubt.” - Abraham Lincoln</message></record>
      <record><index>2027</index><category>facts</category><message>“By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be boss and work twelve hours a day.” - Robert Frost</message></record>
      <record><index>2028</index><category>facts</category><message>“Duct tape is like the force. It has a light side, a dark side, and it holds the universe together.” - Oprah Winfrey</message></record>
      <record><index>2029</index><category>facts</category><message>“Evening news is where they begin with ‘Good evening’, and then proceed to tell you why it isn’t.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2030</index><category>facts</category><message>“Experience is that marvellous thing that enables you to recognize a mistake when you make it again.” - Franklin P. Jones</message></record>
      <record><index>2031</index><category>facts</category><message>“God gave us our relatives; thank God we can choose our friends.” - Ethel Mumford</message></record>
      <record><index>2032</index><category>facts</category><message>“Have no fear of perfection–you’ll never reach it.” – Salvador Dali</message></record>
      <record><index>2033</index><category>facts</category><message>“Hospitality: making your guests feel like they’re at home, even if you wish they were.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2034</index><category>facts</category><message>“I asked God for a bike, but I know God doesn’t work that way. So I stole a bike and asked for forgiveness.” - Emo Philips</message></record>
      <record><index>2035</index><category>facts</category><message>“I couldn’t repair your brakes, so I made your horn louder.” - Steven Wright</message></record>
      <record><index>2036</index><category>facts</category><message>“I didn’t fight my way to the top of the food chain to be a vegetarian.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2037</index><category>facts</category><message>“I discovered I scream the same way whether I’m about to be devoured by a great white shark or if a piece of seaweed touches my foot.” - Axel Rose</message></record>
      <record><index>2038</index><category>facts</category><message>“I don’t suffer from insanity; I enjoy every minute of it.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2039</index><category>facts</category><message>“I hope that after I die, people will say of me: ‘That guy sure owed me a lot of money.’” - Jack Handy</message></record>
      <record><index>2040</index><category>facts</category><message>“I’ve never had a humble opinion. If you’ve got an opinion, why be humble about it?” – Joan Baez</message></record>
      <record><index>2041</index><category>facts</category><message>“If at first you don’t succeed, skydiving is not for you!” - Henny Youngman</message></record>
      <record><index>2042</index><category>facts</category><message>“If I agreed with you we’d both be wrong.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2043</index><category>facts</category><message>“If women ran the world we wouldn’t have wars, just intense negotiations every 28 days.” - Robin Williams</message></record>
      <record><index>2044</index><category>facts</category><message>“If you think nobody cares if you’re alive, try missing a couple of payments.” - Earl Wilson</message></record>
      <record><index>2045</index><category>facts</category><message>“It takes 8,460 bolts to assemble an automobile, and one nut to scatter it all over the road.” – Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2046</index><category>facts</category><message>“It’s true hard work never killed anybody, but I figure, why take the chance?” - Ronald Reagan</message></record>
      <record><index>2047</index><category>facts</category><message>“Keep the dream alive: Hit the snooze button.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2048</index><category>facts</category><message>“Men have two emotions: hungry and horny. If you see him without an erection, make him a sandwich.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2049</index><category>facts</category><message>“Men marry women with the hope they will never change. Women marry men with the hope they will change. Invariably they are both disappointed.” - Albert Einstein</message></record>
      <record><index>2050</index><category>facts</category><message>“Money can’t buy love, but it improves your bargaining position.” - Christopher Marlowe</message></record>
      <record><index>2051</index><category>facts</category><message>“My mother never saw the irony in calling me a son-of-a-bitch.” - Jack Nicholson</message></record>
      <record><index>2052</index><category>facts</category><message>“My opinions may have changed, but not the fact that I am right.” - Ashleigh Brilliant</message></record>
      <record><index>2053</index><category>facts</category><message>“Never go to bed angry, stay awake and plot your revenge.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2054</index><category>facts</category><message>“Patience is something you admire in the driver behind you, but not in one ahead.” - Bill McGlashen</message></record>
      <record><index>2055</index><category>facts</category><message>“People often say that motivation doesn’t last. Well, neither does bathing – that’s why we recommend it daily.” - Zig Ziglar</message></record>
      <record><index>2056</index><category>facts</category><message>“People who think they know everything are a great annoyance to those of us who do.” - Isaac Asimov</message></record>
      <record><index>2057</index><category>facts</category><message>“Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.” - José Maria de Eça de Queiroz</message></record>
      <record><index>2058</index><category>facts</category><message>“Some cause happiness wherever they go; others whenever they go” - Oscar Wilde</message></record>
      <record><index>2059</index><category>facts</category><message>“Sometimes the road less traveled is less traveled for a reason.” - Jerry Seinfeld</message></record>
      <record><index>2060</index><category>facts</category><message>“The best argument against democracy is a five-minute conversation with the average voter.” - Winston Churchill</message></record>
      <record><index>2061</index><category>facts</category><message>“The best way to lie is to tell the truth, carefully edited truth.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2062</index><category>facts</category><message>“The big difference between sex for money and sex for free is that sex for money usually costs a lot less.” - Brendan Behan</message></record>
      <record><index>2063</index><category>facts</category><message>“The early bird might get the worm, but the second mouse gets the cheese.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2064</index><category>facts</category><message>“The hardest thing in the world to understand is income taxes.” - Albert Einstein</message></record>
      <record><index>2065</index><category>facts</category><message>“The human brain is a wonderful thing. It starts working the moment you are born, and never stops until you stand up to speak in public.” - George Jessel</message></record>
      <record><index>2066</index><category>facts</category><message>“The only mystery in life is why the kamikaze pilots wore helmets” - Al McGuire</message></record>
      <record><index>2067</index><category>facts</category><message>“The only way the French are going in is if we tell them we found truffles in Iraq.” - Dennis Miller</message></record>
      <record><index>2068</index><category>facts</category><message>“The quickest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it back in your pocket.” - Will Rogers</message></record>
      <record><index>2069</index><category>facts</category><message>“The sole purpose of a child’s middle name, is so he can tell when he’s really in trouble.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2070</index><category>facts</category><message>“The trouble with being punctual is that nobody’s there to appreciate it.” - Franklin P. Jones</message></record>
      <record><index>2071</index><category>facts</category><message>“Three words guaranteed to humiliate men everywhere: ‘Hold my purse.’” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2072</index><category>facts</category><message>“To be in love is merely to be in a state of perceptual anesthesia.” – H.L. Mencken</message></record>
      <record><index>2073</index><category>facts</category><message>“To steal ideas from one person is plagiarism. To steal from many is research.” - Wilson Mizner</message></record>
      <record><index>2074</index><category>facts</category><message>“We live in a  society where pizza gets to your house before the police.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2075</index><category>facts</category><message>“When I was a boy of fourteen, my father was so ignorant I could hardly stand to have the old man around. But when I got to be twenty-one, I was astonished at how much he had learned in seven years.” - Mark Twain</message></record>
      <record><index>2076</index><category>facts</category><message>“When you go into court, you are putting your fate into the hands of people who weren’t smart enough to get out of jury duty.” - Norm Crosby</message></record>
      <record><index>2077</index><category>facts</category><message>“Why does a woman work ten years to change a man’s habits and then complain that he’s not the man she married?” - Barbra Streisand</message></record>
      <record><index>2078</index><category>facts</category><message>“Why does someone believe you when you say there are four billion stars, but check when you say the paint is wet?” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2079</index><category>facts</category><message>“Why is the place you drive on is a parkway, and the place you park on is the driveway?” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2080</index><category>facts</category><message>“Women who seek to be equal with men lack ambition.” - Marilyn Monroe</message></record>
      <record><index>2081</index><category>facts</category><message>“You are such a good friend that if we were on a sinking ship together and there was only one life jacket… I’d miss you heaps and think of you often.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2082</index><category>facts</category><message>”Children: You spend the first 2 years of their life teaching them to walk and talk. Then you spend the next 16 telling them to sit down and shut-up.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2083</index><category>facts</category><message>”If you die in an elevator, be sure to push the up button.” - Sam Levenson</message></record>
      <record><index>2084</index><category>facts</category><message>”Nothing sucks more than that moment during an argument when you realize you’re wrong” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2085</index><category>facts</category><message>I always take life with a grain of salt, …plus a slice of lemon, …and a shot of tequila.” - Unknown</message></record>
      <record><index>2086</index><category>facts</category><message>“Whether you live to be 50 or 100 makes no difference, if you made no difference in the world.” 
― Jarod Kintz</message></record>
      <record><index>2087</index><category>facts</category><message>“When pointing out the flaws in others, people always end up talking about themselves.”
― Claire Chilton</message></record>
      <record><index>2088</index><category>facts</category><message>“Always borrow money from a pessimist. He won’t expect it back.”- OSCAR WILDE</message></record>
      <record><index>2089</index><category>facts</category><message>“The scientific theory I like best is that the rings of Saturn are composed entirely of lost airline luggage.”
- MARK RUSSELL</message></record>
      <record><index>2090</index><category>facts</category><message>“A successful man is one who makes more money than his wife can spend. A successful woman is one who can find such a man.”
- LANA TURNER</message></record>
      <record><index>2091</index><category>facts</category><message>“By all means, marry. If you get a good wife, you’ll become happy; if you get a bad one, you’ll become a philosopher.”
- SOCRATES</message></record>
      <record><index>2092</index><category>facts</category><message>“Do not argue with an idiot. He will drag you down to his level and beat you with experience.
“- GREG KING</message></record>
      <record><index>2093</index><category>facts</category><message>“Going to church doesn’t make you a Christian any more than standing in a garage makes you a car.
“- BILLY SUNDAY</message></record>
      <record><index>2094</index><category>facts</category><message>“By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be boss and work twelve hours a day.
“- ROBERT FROST</message></record>
      <record><index>2095</index><category>facts</category><message>“The trouble with being punctual is that nobody’s there to appreciate it.”
- FRANKLIN P. JONES</message></record>
      <record><index>2096</index><category>facts</category><message>“The road to success is always under construction.”- Lily Tomlin</message></record>
      <record><index>2097</index><category>facts</category><message>“The difference between stupidity and genius is that genius has its limits.”- Albert Einstein</message></record>
      <record><index>2098</index><category>facts</category><message>“Life is 10% what happens to me and 90% of how I react to it. “–Charles Swindoll</message></record>
      <record><index>2099</index><category>facts</category><message>“Either you run the day, or the day runs you.” –Jim Rohn</message></record>
      <record><index>2100</index><category>facts</category><message>“The man who smiles when things go wrong has thought of someone to blame it on.”- Robert Bloch</message></record>
   </facts>
</head>